Guide to the Ferguson-Edwards family papers
Stanford University Libraries.
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives.
Ferguson-Edwards family papers
1898-1986
SC1239
2 Linear feet
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives. Stanford University Libraries. 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: speccollref@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical/Historical note
Agnes Ferguson (Hunter) earned an AB in Latin in 1898.
Amy Parker Ferguson earned an AB in English in 1902. Harry James Edwards earned an AB in History in 1901. The two were married April 30, 1907.
Amy McNeil Edwards earned an AB in Social Sciences in 1936.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of student materials belonging to Agnes Ferguson, Amy Ferguson, Harry James Edwards, and Amy McNeil Edwards. These items document student life at Stanford between the late 1890s to the 1930s. Also included are reunion materials for the class of 1936 from 1956 and 1986.
Access Terms
Edwards, Amy McNeil; Edwards, Harry James; Ferguson, Amy; Hunter, Agnes Ferguson.; Diplomas.; Sorority - Alpha Phi; Stanford University--Students.; Student life.; Women college students--California--Stanford.
Collection Contents
- M.A. Ferguson - incoming letters, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Agnes Ferguson - photograph, circa 1898 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Agnes Eva Ferguson - teacher certificate, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Agnes Eva Ferguson - diploma, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Amy Ferguson - Alpha Phi material, 1899-1901 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Harry James Edwards - photograph, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Harry James Edwards - miscellaneous, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Harry James Edwards - Delta Kappa Epsilon shareholder certificates, 1922-1930 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Amy McNeil Edwards - diploma, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Amy Edwards - Certificate of Registration cards, 1933-1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Amy Edwards - accounting records, 1933-1936 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Amy Edwards - class event programs and flyers, 1932-1936 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Amy Edwards - commencement material, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Amy Edwards - drama/theater programs, 1933-1936 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Amy Edwards - registration documents, 1933-1936 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Amy Edwards - Alumni Association material, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
- The San Francisco Junior Auxiliary to the Stanford Convalescent Home, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Stanford Ephemera - stationery (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Stanford Ephemera - decals, seals, stickers (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Stanford Ephemera - button (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Alpha Phi - miscellaneous material (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Social Standards of Stanford University & Regulations of Organized Women Students of Stanford, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Photograph (unidentified woman), undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Class of 1936 - 20th Reunion Bawl Out, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Class of 1936 - 50th Reunion (speech typescript), 1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Class of 1936 - 50th Reunion The Stanford '36er, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Clippings, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Amy Ferguson - Stanford's Pipe and Bowl, circa 1903 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Amy Edwards - scrapbook, 1932-1936 (Box 2)
- Photograph - unidentified women, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Photographs - Stanford campus, before 1906 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Amy P. Ferguson, circa 1900 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Amy M. Edwards - Student handbook, 1932-1933 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Class of 1935 - Senior Dance dance book (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Commencent program, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Varsity football schedule, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Class of 1937 Junior Prom dance book, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 8)